Lesson 48, the silent village, in this much-traveled world.
第48课，寂静的村庄，在这个漫长的世界中。
inaccessible: adj. 难接近的,达不到的
There are still thousands of places which are inaccessible to tourists.
仍然有成千上万个游客无法进入的地方。
hospitable: adj. 不好客的
We always assume that villagers in remote places are friendly and hospitable.
我们总是假设偏远地区的村民很友好且热情好客。
But people who are cut off not only from foreign tourists, but even from their own countrymen
但是，不仅被外国游客隔绝的人，甚至与自己的同胞隔绝
hostile: adj. 不友好的,有敌意的
can be hostile to travelers.
可能对旅行者有敌意。
Visits to really remote villages are seldom enjoyable, as my wife and I discovered during
我和我的妻子在我妻子期间发现的，对真正偏远的村庄的访问很少
a tour.
游览。
Through the Balkans, we had spent several days in a small town and visited a number of
通过巴尔干，我们在一个小镇上度过了几天，并参观了许多
vicinity: n.   周围,近邻
old churches in the vicinity.
附近的老教堂。
These attracted many visitors.
这些吸引了许多游客。
architectural: adj. 建筑的
For they were not only of great architectural interest, but contained a large number of
因为它们不仅具有极大的建筑兴趣，而且包含了很多
fresco: n.   壁画
beautifully preserved frescoes as well.
保存精美的壁画。
On the day before our departure, several busloads of tourists descended on the town.
在我们离开的前一天，几个游客降落在镇上。
This was more than we could bear.
这超出了我们的忍受。
So we decided to spend our last day exploring the countryside, taking a path which led
因此，我们决定花最后一天探索乡村，走一条路。
out of the town.
出门在城里。
We crossed a few fields until we came to a dense wood.
我们越过了几个田地，直到我们来到一块茂密的木头。
abruptly: adv. 突然地,意外地
We expected the path to end abruptly.
我们期望突然结束的道路。
But we found that it traced its way through the trees.
但是我们发现它可以追溯到树木。
tramp: v.   徒步行进
We tramped through the wood for over two hours until we arrived at a deep stream.
我们在木头上擦了两个多小时，直到我们到达一条深溪。
We could see that the path continued on the other side.
我们可以看到这条路在另一侧继续。
But we had no idea how we could get across the stream.
但是我们不知道如何跨越流。
moor: v.   （用绳、链、锚）系（船）
Suddenly my wife spotted a boat moored to the bank.
突然，我的妻子发现一艘停泊在银行的船。
In it there was a boatman fast asleep.
里面有一个船夫快速入睡。
ferry: v.   （用渡船）运
We gently woke him up and asked him to ferry us to the other side.
我们轻轻地叫醒他，要求他将我们渡到另一边。
Though he was reluctant to do so at first, we eventually persuaded him to take us.
尽管他最初不愿这样做，但我们最终说服了他带我们。
The path led to a tiny village perched on the steep sides of a mountain.
这条小路导致一个小村庄栖息在山的陡峭侧面。
rag: n.   破烂衣服
The place consisted of a straggling unmade road which was lined on either side by small
这个地方由一条散乱的道路组成
houses.
房屋。
Even under a clear blue sky, the village looked forbidding.
即使在晴朗的蓝天下，村庄也看上去很禁止。
As all the houses were built of grey mud bricks, the village seemed deserted.
当所有房屋都是用灰色泥砖建造的，村庄似乎荒芜了。
The only sign of life being an ugly looking black goat on a short length of rope tied to
生命的唯一迹象是一只丑陋的黑山羊
a tree in.
一棵树。
A field nearby, sitting down on a dilapidated wooden fence near the field, we opened a couple
附近的一个田野，坐在田野附近的破旧木栅栏上，我们打开了一对夫妇
sardine: n.   沙丁鱼，沙丁鱼罐头
of tins of sardines and had a picnic lunch.
沙丁鱼的罐头，吃了野餐午餐。
While at once, I noticed that my wife seemed to be filled with alarm.
同时，我注意到我的妻子似乎充满了警报。
rag: n.   破烂衣服
Looking up I saw that we were surrounded by children and rags who were looking at us
抬头看，我看到我们被看着我们的孩子和抹布包围着
silently as we.
像我们一样默默地。
Eight, we offered them food and spoke to them kindly.
八，我们为他们提供食物，并与他们交谈。
But they remained motionless.
但是他们仍然一动不动。
I concluded that they were simply shy of strangers.
我得出的结论是，他们只是害羞的陌生人。
When we later walked down the main street of the villager, we were followed by a silent
当我们后来沿着村民的主要街道行走时，我们被沉默
procession: adj. 不动的
procession of children.
儿童游行。
The village which had seemed deserted, immediately came to life.
这个村庄似乎荒废了，立即栩栩如生。
Faces appeared at windows.
面孔出现在窗户上。
Men in shirtsleeves stood outside their houses and glared at us.
穿着衬衫的男人站在他们的房屋外面，瞪着我们。
shawl: n.   披巾，围巾
Old women in black shawls appeared at us from doorways.
穿着黑色披肩的老妇从门口出现在我们身上。
The most frightening thing of all was that not a sound could be heard.
最令人恐惧的是，无法听到声音。
There was no doubt that we were unwelcome visitors.
毫无疑问，我们是不受欢迎的游客。
We needed no further warning.
我们不需要进一步的警告。
Turning back down the main street.
转向主要街道。
quicken: v.   加快
We quickened our pace and made our way rapidly towards the stream where we hoped the boatman
我们加快了步伐，并迅速朝着我们希望船夫的溪流迈进
was.
曾是。
Waiting.
等待。